const level21questions = [
     

  {
    "question": "2.3 + 9.1 = ?",
    "options": ["11.4", "9", "9.1", "14.2"],
    "answer": "11.4"
  },
  {
    "question": "5.7 + 1.7 = ?",
    "options": ["15.8", "12.2", "7.4", "4.1"],
    "answer": "7.4"
  },
  {
    "question": "9.3 + 1.6 = ?",
    "options": ["9.3", "10.9", "2.5", "4.8"],
    "answer": "10.9"
  },
  {
    "question": "0.4 + 5.0 = ?",
    "options": ["6.6", "10.2", "5.4", "18.6"],
    "answer": "5.4"
  },
  {
    "question": "8.5 + 4.3 = ?",
    "options": ["12.8", "10.8", "12.1", "8.8"],
    "answer": "12.8"
  },
  {
    "question": "7.1 + 1.7 = ?",
    "options": ["8.6", "8.8", "6.6", "16.7"],
    "answer": "8.8"
  },
  {
    "question": "1.5 + 1.8 = ?",
    "options": ["13", "3.3", "17.9", "8.8"],
    "answer": "3.3"
  },
  {
    "question": "9.7 + 1.8 = ?",
    "options": ["11.3", "2.8", "11.5", "13.1"],
    "answer": "11.5"
  },
  {
    "question": "0.6 + 2.2 = ?",
    "options": ["2.8", "15.9", "13", "12.7"],
    "answer": "2.8"
  },
  {
    "question": "1.5 + 4.3 = ?",
    "options": ["5.8", "16.7", "4.4", "9.6"],
    "answer": "5.8"
  },
  {
    "question": "3.1 + 5.0 = ?",
    "options": ["11.4", "8.3", "10", "8.1"],
    "answer": "8.1"
  },
  {
    "question": "5.7 + 1.6 = ?",
    "options": ["18.3", "12.1", "7.3", "4.7"],
    "answer": "7.3"
  },
  {
    "question": "7.7 + 1.2 = ?",
    "options": ["8.9", "7.8", "9.6", "10.7"],
    "answer": "8.9"
  },
  {
    "question": "2.5 + 0.4 = ?",
    "options": ["15.1", "2.9", "6.9", "10.4"],
    "answer": "2.9"
  },
  {
    "question": "7.8 + 6.6 = ?",
    "options": ["14.4", "15.9", "9.4", "18.1"],
    "answer": "14.4"
  },
  {
    "question": "8.9 + 1.3 = ?",
    "options": ["9", "10.2", "8.6", "11.5"],
    "answer": "10.2"
  },
  {
    "question": "4.0 + 5.5 = ?",
    "options": ["9.5", "8.5", "7.3", "4.2"],
    "answer": "9.5"
  },
  {
    "question": "8.7 + 9.5 = ?",
    "options": ["18.2", "9.9", "2", "11.5"],
    "answer": "18.2"
  },
  {
    "question": "7.1 + 2.0 = ?",
    "options": ["15.1", "10.3", "14.2", "9.1"],
    "answer": "9.1"
  },

   {
        "question": "6.0 + 0.5 = ?",
        "options": ["11.5", "6.5", "1.3", "10.9"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "7.6 + 7.6 = ?",
        "options": ["3.6", "8.8", "9.2", "15.2"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "2.5 + 0.2 = ?",
        "options": ["11.6", "2.7", "13.4", "3"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "6.1 + 4.7 = ?",
        "options": ["10.8", "8", "12.5", "12.1"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "0.7 + 8.9 = ?",
        "options": ["15.1", "9", "9.6", "7.6"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "0.8 + 0.7 = ?",
        "options": ["17.7", "10.1", "15.2", "1.5"],
        "answer": "D"
    },

 {
        "question": "2.8 + 2.3 = ?",
        "options": ["10.5", "15.1", "5.1", "12.1"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "4.6 + 3.0 = ?",
        "options": ["7.6", "11.9", "10", "13.9"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "8.3 + 4.9 = ?",
        "options": ["13.2", "14.3", "15.4", "5.5"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "9.6 + 1.0 = ?",
        "options": ["17.3", "19.3", "9.7", "10.6"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "6.4 + 0.4 = ?",
        "options": ["7.8", "11.6", "5.4", "6.8"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "1.6 + 5.2 = ?",
        "options": ["14.5", "6.8", "8.1", "9.8"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "6.6 + 1.1 = ?",
        "options": ["6.4", "7.7", "11", "8.8"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "0.9 + 4.2 = ?",
        "options": ["5.1", "16.8", "12.8", "10.7"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "6.9 + 9.5 = ?",
        "options": ["6.4", "14.1", "6.2", "16.4"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "8.2 + 8.0 = ?",
        "options": ["7", "13.2", "16.2", "10"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "5.6 + 9.5 = ?",
        "options": ["4.1", "1.8", "15.1", "8.9"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "7.1 + 5.0 = ?",
        "options": ["15.7", "12.7", "8.9", "12.1"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "6.3 + 0.5 = ?",
        "options": ["9.5", "6.3", "6.8", "17.7"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "1.5 + 7.4 = ?",
        "options": ["6.2", "3.2", "13.3", "8.9"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "6.2 + 9.4 = ?",
        "options": ["10.5", "15.6", "8.1", "14.1"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "8.3 + 2.8 = ?",
        "options": ["13.1", "12.5", "9.5", "11.1"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "0.7 + 8.5 = ?",
        "options": ["8.2", "13.1", "9.2", "10.2"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "1.8 + 1.3 = ?",
        "options": ["11.6", "15.7", "3.1", "9.5"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "2.2 + 3.7 = ?",
        "options": ["5.9", "10.7", "8.7", "11.5"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "4.4 + 5.7 = ?",
        "options": ["5.8", "14.5", "4.2", "10.1"],
        "answer": "D"
},

 {
        "question": "2.0 + 6.2 = ?",
        "options": ["9.9", "8.9", "8.2", "13.1"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "6.8 + 2.5 = ?",
        "options": ["8.6", "18.4", "14.5", "9.3"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "7.2 + 4.1 = ?",
        "options": ["6.2", "6.8", "17.4", "11.3"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "4.3 + 4.3 = ?",
        "options": ["8.6", "11.7", "4.7", "17.8"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "8.9 + 3.5 = ?",
        "options": ["12.4", "8.1", "5.9", "9.7"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "5.3 + 4.4 = ?",
        "options": ["6.6", "9.7", "4.3", "10.7"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "2.1 + 6.3 = ?",
        "options": ["6.5", "7.4", "8.4", "15.6"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "8.4 + 1.6 = ?",
        "options": ["7.1", "4.3", "14.6", "10"],
        "answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "0.9 + 6.8 = ?",
        "options": ["13.2", "10.5", "7.7", "3.4"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "5.3 + 9.9 = ?",
        "options": ["15.2", "10.9", "12.5", "19.1"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "4.7 + 9.3 = ?",
        "options": ["14", "8.3", "15.5", "6.3"],
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "8.3 + 5.6 = ?",
        "options": ["12.8", "16.5", "13.9", "4"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "2.0 + 9.1 = ?",
        "options": ["12", "6.7", "11.1", "9.9"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "6.6 + 8.2 = ?",
        "options": ["7.8", "6.2", "14.8", "10.4"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "0.4 + 4.5 = ?",
        "options": ["16.7", "11.1", "4.9", "12.8"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "3.8 + 3.1 = ?",
        "options": ["13", "6.9", "8", "9.5"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "9.4 + 0.6 = ?",
        "options": ["11.1", "5.2", "10", "8.1"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "2.7 + 0.4 = ?",
        "options": ["8.1", "3.1", "9.6", "7.2"],
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "8.6 + 1.1 = ?",
        "options": ["10.6", "17.3", "9.7", "10.3"],
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "5.9 + 3.6 = ?",
        "options": ["14", "9.5", "9.8", "11.6"],
        "answer": "B"
    },

 
        {
            "question": "After 66?",
            "options": ["15.6", "7.7", "12.7", "11.5"],
            "answer": "11.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 67?",
            "options": ["7.4", "13.5", "13.3", "9"],
            "answer": "9"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 68?",
            "options": ["12.8", "9.8", "11.8", "1.2"],
            "answer": "1.2"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 69?",
            "options": ["9.7", "10.3", "6.5", "7.6"],
            "answer": "7.6"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 70?",
            "options": ["13.8", "7", "10.8", "16.8"],
            "answer": "10.8"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 71?",
            "options": ["8.7", "11.6", "6.4", "9.6"],
            "answer": "8.7"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 72?",
            "options": ["10.5", "11.3", "17.4", "11.2"],
            "answer": "11.3"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 73?",
            "options": ["12", "11.6", "10.6", "3"],
            "answer": "12"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 74?",
            "options": ["14.3", "2.8", "3.4", "10.2"],
            "answer": "10.2"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 75?",
            "options": ["7", "12.8", "18.4", "10.1"],
            "answer": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 76?",
            "options": ["5.9", "4", "14.7", "8.1"],
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 77?",
            "options": ["12.5", "12", "8.1", "15.4"],
            "answer": "8.1"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 78?",
            "options": ["7.8", "5.4", "16.3", "12.4"],
            "answer": "16.3"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 79?",
            "options": ["15.6", "9.6", "9.2", "8.2"],
            "answer": "8.2"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 80?",
            "options": ["13.3", "9.5", "6.1", "15.4"],
            "answer": "9.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 81?",
            "options": ["10.7", "13.2", "9.5", "8.2"],
            "answer": "9.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 82?",
            "options": ["13.3", "8.2", "18.6", "3"],
            "answer": "18.6"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 83?",
            "options": ["10.2", "13.6", "7.6", "14.5"],
            "answer": "14.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 84?",
            "options": ["9", "12.9", "10.3", "7.3"],
            "answer": "12.9"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 85?",
            "options": ["11.7", "5.7", "11", "4.8"],
            "answer": "4.8"
     }, 

        {
            "question": "After 86?",
            "options": ["11.8", "9.2", "7.2", "9.9"],
            "answer": "9.2"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 87?",
            "options": ["11", "5.2", "6.1", "11.5"],
            "answer": "11.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 88?",
            "options": ["4.9", "8", "9.4", "12.4"],
            "answer": "12.4"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 89?",
            "options": ["11", "12.3", "10.8", "2.3"],
            "answer": "10.8"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 90?",
            "options": ["13.1", "14.4", "5.9", "7.5"],
            "answer": "13.1"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 91?",
            "options": ["9.2", "7.8", "7", "12"],
            "answer": "7"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 92?",
            "options": ["10.8", "6.5", "7.7", "13"],
            "answer": "6.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 93?",
            "options": ["8.4", "17.3", "6.2", "13"],
            "answer": "13"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 94?",
            "options": ["12.7", "8.2", "7.6", "9.6"],
            "answer": "12.7"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 95?",
            "options": ["4.2", "8.4", "5.8", "8.3"],
            "answer": "8.3"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 96?",
            "options": ["9.7", "16.1", "10.6", "13.7"],
            "answer": "16.1"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 97?",
            "options": ["11.3", "10.5", "13.8", "11.6"],
            "answer": "13.8"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 98?",
            "options": ["3.1", "16.3", "13.4", "8.8"],
            "answer": "3.1"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 99?",
            "options": ["6.5", "12", "3", "16.4"],
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "After 100?",
            "options": ["8.7", "15.6", "7.8", "15.5"],
            "answer": "15.6"
        },
];
export default level21questions;